dirwell.com 2018-07-08

# - Privacy Policy Directory Well - Web Directory

List your business

Your privacy is important to **Directory Well Web Directory**. We promise to protect your private information. This Privacy Policy is meant to give a description of the information we collect from you, how we may use that information, with whom we may share it, and your options pertaining to the use and disclosure of your information.

We encourage you to carefully read this Privacy Policy before using our website, services, or entering into any sort of business with us. By using our website, you declare your acceptance of the terms within the Privacy Policy.

### Personally Identifying Information Collection

The information collected by **DirWell** depends solely on your use of our directory.

  * If you sign up to receive our e-Newsletter as a free user of our directory, you are required to enter your full name and email address.
  * You may have to submit your personal information when submitting forms, registration, inquiry forms, subscriptions, regular updates and emails.
  * If you submit your website for listing in our web directory, we collect personal information, your full name, email address, site URL and credit card information.

 **DirWell** uses all the information collected for the purposes of billing, providing services, identification and authentication, sending the eNewsletter, and contact.

 **DirWell** never shares your personal information or email addresses with any third parties, except service providers, such as the credit-card payment processors who carry on functions on our behalf. They need access to your personal information to perform their job, but they do not have permission to use, share, distribute or sell this information for any other purposes.

### Personal Data Security

For your protection, we take appropriate electronic, physical and other high-level security measures to help safeguard all your billing and other information from unauthorized access, disclosure or alteration. We use strong firewalls to help prevent any unauthorized access to your personal information.

We use SSL encryption to transmit all of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours. Our website is highly protected from any breaches in security.

### Disclosure Of Data

Personally identifiable information is disclosed by **DirWell** only under certain circumstances, where there is need to comply with subpoenas, warrants, and other legal processes, or when you violate the Terms of Service given on our website. Sharing this information may become necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action on any actual or suspected illegal activities.

In addition, certain information may be disclosed to service providers, such as credit-card payment processors who perform services for us. The information needed by these service providers to perform their functions, is given access to, but they are not given the permission to share this information or use it in any other way.

### Third Parties

 **DirWell** uses hosting partners and other third party vendors to offer the related networking and technology required to run **DirWell** Web Directory. Users' activity information on our website may be shared with our advertisers or partners (if any), in order to see the most viewed pages, browser information and search engine usage, number of repeat and unique visitors etc. This is done to improve our website and serve our clients and users better.

Our directory also contains links to third-party websites in the form of advertisers, submitted sites and informational sites. We make sure the sites we link to are genuine. However, we don't take responsibility for any privacy breach on such websites or the use of your personal information collected on their websites. We suggest you read the privacy policy and terms of use of any website visited through our links.

### Email Information Security

Your email information is not shared by **DirWell** with any third parties, except the service providers that act on our behalf, such as the credit-card payment processors. These service providers may have access to your personal information to perform their duties, but they are not permitted to share this information with anyone else or use it for anything other than the intended purpose.

The email address collected from you on **DirWell** for any purpose, will only be used to contact subscribers for the purpose intended when entering it on our website, and for nothing else. If you wish not to receive such emails from us, you have the right to unsubscribe at any moment.

In any event that you receive an email that appears to have been sent by **DirWell** or people associated with **DirWell** , and it reeks of spam, please let us know by using the _[Contact Us](http://www.dirwell.com/contact.php)_ button on our website.

In case of any changes made to your personal information, change in email address or payment/billing details or anything else, you can update that information by using the _[Contact Us](http://www.dirwell.com/contact.php)_ option.

### You Agree

Any changes to the Privacy Policy on **DirWell** will become effective the minute they are posted on the website. It is your responsibility to keep track and be in the know of any such policy changes.

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection and use of information on our website. Please be assured that **DirWell** takes all reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our website or anything within, including our services, you declare your unconditional agreement with our Privacy Policy.

#### NEWS

Visit our newsroom to learn what we've been up to, what we're planning next, and what others are saying about us.

#### CONTACT US

Have questions, comments, or suggestions for us? We’d love to hear from you. 

 Drop Us A Line 

#### CAREERS

Explore Dirwell careers—and find out how you can spend your days helping businesses succeed and connect with their customers.
